<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="7.0.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">Steroid use in MLB has significantly damaged the integrity of the sport.</statement>
     <statement id="2">Players who used steroids should not be eligible for the Hall of Fame.</statement>
     <statement id="3">MLB players should be allowed to use steroids if it’s regulated and monitored.</statement>
     <statement id="4">The focus on steroid use in MLB distracts from the real issues facing the game, like fan engagement.</statement>
     <statement id="5">Players who used steroids should face lifetime bans from MLB.</statement>
     <statement id="6">MLB&apos;s punishment for steroid use should be more lenient to encourage rehabilitation, not just penalties.</statement>
     <statement id="7">Steroid use in MLB has leveled the playing field for players who are naturally less gifted.</statement>
     <statement id="8">The media has exaggerated the role of steroids in MLB, when it’s really just a small portion of the game.</statement>
     <statement id="9">The pressure to perform at an elite level in MLB contributes to steroid use among players.</statement>
     <statement id="10">There should be a separate category in the Hall of Fame for players who were involved in the steroid era.</statement>
     <statement id="11">Steroid use in MLB has become a public relations issue, more than a real problem.</statement>
     <statement id="12">MLB has taken appropriate action to combat steroid use and ensure the fairness of the game.</statement>
     <statement id="13">The use of steroids should be decriminalized in MLB to promote transparency and fairness.</statement>
     <statement id="14">Steroid use was rampant in MLB during the late 1990s and early 2000s, and this should be acknowledged.</statement>
     <statement id="15">MLB should introduce stricter drug testing to ensure that players remain drug-free.</statement>
     <statement id="16">There is no clear evidence that steroids directly lead to improved performance in MLB.</statement>
     <statement id="17">Steroid use should be allowed for players who are injured and seeking recovery.</statement>
     <statement id="18">MLB should support players who want to quit using steroids through better health and wellness programs.</statement>
     <statement id="19">The use of steroids should result in a temporary suspension, not a permanent ban.</statement>
     <statement id="20">MLB has done enough to educate players about the risks and consequences of steroid use.</statement>
   </statements>